<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ching-Chia Renn</title>
    <link>https://renncc.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ching-Chia Renn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 16:39:19 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://renncc.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Cluster</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/the_cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/the_cluster/</guid>
      <description>The Cluster 觸簇 06 / 2018
If an object can sense human behavior, what reaction will it give to you? If an inanimate being exists as a humanoid, what kind of existence would it be? 如果物件能夠感知人的行為，它會給你什麼樣的回應？如果一個非生命作為一個類生命的存在，它會是個怎麼樣的存在？
The device uses the conductive cloth developed by Far Eastern New Century to study the possibilites of this material and apply it to the sensations of touch and pressure of objects.
Many individuals from a group whereas each of them is an independent existence, but mutually influencinge each other in the group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pillow Fight!</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/pillow_fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/pillow_fight/</guid>
      <description>Pillow Fight! I wanna play together! 枕頭戰！我要我們憶起玩！ 04 / 2019
Pillow Fight is a inter-generational game which is including pillows as operating interface and a tablet. We emphasize care between generations, with the main goal of allowing the elderly to enjoy the time with their family and enhance the relationship while exercising their physical bodies.
We propose the concept that adaptive design with technology should be hidden in our daily life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AR Chinese Dictionary</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/ar_dict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/ar_dict/</guid>
      <description>AR Chinese Dictionary - Chinese Character in Childhood AR中文字典 - 漢字小時候 12 / 2018
It is an app designed for non-Chinese native speakers. Through the mobile device to learn Chinese characters with AR from the earliest Chinese character. The characteristics of the &amp;ldquo;pictogram&amp;rdquo; fully express the beauty of the Chinese character. The content of application is simple and easy to understand. There are more images and pictures replace the text descriptions, so that beginners who learn Chinese can easily get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-power Vehicle</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/nonpower_vehicle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/nonpower_vehicle/</guid>
      <description>Non-power Vehicle 無動力車 06 / 2017
&amp;lt; S W I N G &amp;gt;
Like a fish roaming in water. 如魚在水中翱游般。
The vehicle is a device for spatial switching, which can bring the human body or consciousness to other places, experiencing the continuous change of feeling by the process of spatial replacement.
&amp;ldquo;Experiencing the journey of transportation&amp;rdquo;, our vehicle travels by using &amp;ldquo;body&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;feeling&amp;rdquo; to strengthen the body&amp;rsquo;s feelings.
The relationship between the vehicle and the rider is like &amp;ldquo;fish&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;fishtail&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entropy</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/entropy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/entropy/</guid>
      <description>Entropy 09 / 2019
This world is changing always. The change was predictable at the first time, but it gradually became uncertain.
How can we create an uncertain phenomenon with a certain dynamic?
Entropy is a quantitative measure of disorder. —— Efstathios E. Michaelides
Order and disorder are just a relative concept, actually, there is only more order and less order.
Making a cycle of switching in order and disorder. Even if it is a cycle of order and disorder, the order and disorder in every time are different existences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AR Poetry Teaching System</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/ar_poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:56:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/ar_poetry/</guid>
      <description>Taoyuan Poetry: AR Teaching System 桃園「塘」詩：AR教學系統 12 / 2018
The main purpose of this system development is to enhance the interaction of literary poetry teaching and learning motivation through the assistance of personal mobile devices and the experience of the landscape field.
This system is an innovative teaching of AR interaction for cross-disciplinary collaboration between design and literature. By designing the three-dimensional imagery in the poetry, and then superimposing the virtual scene on the real scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gloves 復健手套</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/work7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/work7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;under construction&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D列印胸花 - 設計與製造</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/work8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/work8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;under construction&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robot Arm Coffee Show</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/work9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/work9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;under construction&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridge &lt;KNOT&gt;</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/bridge/</guid>
      <description>Bridge 01 / 2017
Knot is a posture to burst out; extension is a process to proceed.
Bridge has a meaning of connection between two places which is a symbol of going across barriers; it is the concept of going from one point to another. In this project, we hope to show the feeling of convergence and curling up before extending, just like the appearance of “knot”.
Starting with the concept of &amp;ldquo;knot&amp;rdquo;, in addition to creating the feeling of gathering and visual extension, making a contrast between psychological feeling and actual shape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Item without image</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/work11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:50:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/work11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;under construction&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Item without image</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/project/work12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/project/work12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;under construction&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post_test</title>
      <link>https://renncc.github.io/post/post_test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 16:39:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renncc.github.io/post/post_test/</guid>
      <description>this is the first post test. 20221030 test.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
